A Guide to the Governor Gerald L. Baliles Executive Papers, 1986-1990
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: 1989 (accession 33707)
  - Sub-Series E: Cabinet
    - Correspondence and Memorandums send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 December 29-July 5 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums send and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 June 27-January 10 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Correspondence - Economic Development, 1989 December 28-September 13 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Correspondence - Economic Development, 1989 September 6-June 1 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Correspondence - Economic Development, 1989 May 31-January 3 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - E.2 - Secretary of Economic Development - State Agencies
    - Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services (part one) (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services (part two) (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Pesticides (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Department of Commerce (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Department of Economic Development - Correspondence (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Department of Economic Development - England/France Trip (European Trade Mission to Belgium, Britain, Denmark and West German, 1989 July 4-15) (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Department of Economic Development - Italy/Egypt Trip (Mediterrean Trade Mission to Egypt, Italy and Turkey, 1989 March 9-19) (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Department of Economic Development - Japan-Virginia Society (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Department of Economic Development - Southeast United States/Japan Association (SEUS/Japan) (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Department of Economic Development - Taiwan (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Department of Economic Development - Division of Tourism (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Department of Economic Development - Virginia Film Office (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Department of Forestry (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Department of Labor and Industry (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Department of Mines, Minerals and Energy (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Department of Minority Business Enterprise (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Department of World Trade (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Employment Commission (part one) (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Employment Commission (part two) (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Port Authority (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Port Authority - Inland Port (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - E.2 - Secretary of Economic Development - Topics
    - Appalachian Regional Commission (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Housing - General (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - International Trade (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Plant Closing/Staff Reductions (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Space (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 December 29-November 17 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 November 16-August 23 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 August 15-May 10 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 April 27-January 18 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Correspondence, 1989 December 21-October 13 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Correspondence, 1989 October 12-March 12 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Correspondence, 1989 March 20-January 3 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - Colleges and Universities
    - General (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - State Council of Higher Education (part one) (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - State Council of Higher Education (part two) (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Christopher Newport College (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - George Mason University (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - James Madison University (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Longwood College (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Mary Washington College (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Medical College of Virginia - See Virginia Commonwealth University
    - Norfolk State University (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Old Dominion University (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Radford University (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - University of Virginia (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University/Medical College of Virginia (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Community College System (VCCS) (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Virginia State University (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - College of William and Mary (part one) (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - College of William and Mary (part two) (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - Education Topics
    - Education Commission of the States (ECS) (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - International Education (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Literacy Program (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Museum of American Frontier Culture (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - University of the 21st Century (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - E.3 - Secretary of Education - State Agencies
    - Department of Education (part one) (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Department of Education (part two) (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Science Museum of Virginia (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - State Board of Education (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Educational Loan Authority (VELA) (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives (part one) (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Virginia State Library and Archives (part two) (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - E.4 - Secretary of Finance
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 December 6-September 15 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 September 13-January 9 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - E.4 - Secretary of Finance - State Agencies
    - Department of Accounts - Comptroller (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Department of Planning and Budget (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Department of the State Internal Auditor (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Department of Taxation (part one) (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Department of Taxation (part two) (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Department of Taxation (part three) (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Department of Taxation (part four) (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Treasury (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Treasury - Division of Unclaimed Property (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - E.4 - Secretary of Finance - Finance Topics
    - Budget Requests (part one) (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Budget Requests (part two) (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Budget Requests (part three) (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Budget Requests (part four) (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Local Option Tax (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Lottery Revenue (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Pensions (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Veterans' Home (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Health and Human Resources
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 December 29-October 3 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 September 28-July 13 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 July 12-January 13 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Health and Human Resources - State Agencies
    - Council on Indians (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Department for the Aging (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Department for Children (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Department for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Department of Health (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Department of Health Professionals (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Department of Medical Assistance Services (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services (part one) (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services (part two) (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services (part three) (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Department of Rehabilitative Services (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Department for the Rights of the Disabled (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Department of Social Services (part one) (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Department of Social Services (part two) (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Department of Social Services (part three) (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Department for the Visually Handicapped (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Department of Volunteerism (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Department (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Department - Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA) (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - E.5 - Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Topics
    - Abortion (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - AIDS (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Certificate of Public Need (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Community Action Agencies (Box 174a, Folder 1)
    - Council on Child Day Care and Early Childhood Development Programs (Box 174a, Folder 2)
    - Drug and Alcohol Abuse (Box 174a, Folder 3)
    - Infant Mortality (Box 174a, Folder 4)
    - School Based Health Centers (Box 174a, Folder 5)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 December 29-August 29 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 August 28-January 9 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - Boards and Commissions
    - Chesapeake Bay - General and Chesapeake Bay Executive Council (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act and Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Potomac River Fisheries Commission (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - State Agencies
    - Council on the Environment (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Department of Conservation and Recreation (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Department of Games and Inland Fisheries (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Department of Historic Resources (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Department of Parks and Recreation (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Department of Waste Management (part one) (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Department of Waste Management (part two) (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - State Water Control Board (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Marine Resources Commission (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - Topics
    - Back Bay Wildlife Refuge (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Bass Masters Fishing Tournament (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Chesapeake Bay Fishing Tournament (Governor's Cup) (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Oil Drilling (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Kiptopeke Site (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Lake Gaston (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Lee County Landfill (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - School of the Bay (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Wildlife Refuges (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 December 29-October 10 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 October 6-July 6 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1989 July 5-January 17 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Governor's Correspondence, 1989 December 29-August 11 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Correspondence, 1989 August 9-January 12 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety - State Agencies
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Board of Corrections (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Commonwealth Transportation Board (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Department of Aviation (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Department of Corrections (part one) (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Department of Corrections (part two) (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Department of Corrections - Expansion of Culpeper Field Unit (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Department of Corrections - Prison Overcrowding (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Department of Correctional Education (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Department of Emergency Services (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Emergency Situation, December 1989 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Floods, 1989 June 14-15 in Loudoun and Fairfax (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Flood, 1989 July 20 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Flood, 1989 October 20, Buchanan (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Hurricane Hugo (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Department of Emergency Services - Virginia Beach (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Department of Fire Programs (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Department of Military Affairs (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part one) (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part two) (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part three) (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Department of State Police (part one) (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Department of State Police (part two) (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Department of State Police (part three) (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Department of State Police - Narcotics Trust Fund (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Department of Transportation (part one) (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Department of Transportation (part two) (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Department of Transportation (part three) (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Department of Transportation (part four) (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Department of Transportation (part five) (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Department of Transportation - I-66 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Department of Transportation - Ridgefield Road (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Department of Transportation - Route 29 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Department of Transportation - Route 58 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Department of Transportation - Washington Bypass Study (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Council, Briefing Material for 1 December 1989 meeting (part one) (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Council (part two) (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety - Topics
    - Coleman Bridge (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Commuter Rail Service (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Firearms (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - High Occupancy Vehicles (HOV) (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Metro-Washington Airport Authority (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - National Guard (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Nopwasky (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Railroads/Railways - General (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Speed Limit (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Thompson Cemetery (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series F: General Assembly
    - General Correspondence (part one) (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence (part two) (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence (part three) (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - House of Delegates Correspondence, A-C (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - House of Delegates Correspondence, D-M (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - House of Delegates Correspondence, O-W (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Senate Correspondence, A-F (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Senate Correspondence, G-M (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Senate Correspondence, N-W (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series G: Secretary of the Commonwealth
    - Appointments and Correspondence (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series H: Legislative
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Division of Capitol Police (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series I: Attorney General
    - Correspondence (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series J: Judicial
    - General/Courts (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Virginia State Bar (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series K: Independent State Agencies
    - Department of Worker's Compensation - Industrial Commission of Virginia (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - State Corporation Commission - General (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - State Corporation Commission - Bureau of Financial Institutions (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - State Corporation Commission - Bureau of Insurance (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - State Corporation Commission - Division of Energy Regulations (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - State Lottery Department (part one) (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - State Lottery Department (part two) (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - State Lottery Department (part three) (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Racing Commission (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series L: Lt. Governor
    - L. Douglas Wilder (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series M: Virginia Liaison Office
    - Correspondence and Memorandums, 1989 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series N: United States Government
    - Senate - General (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Senate - John W. Warner (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Senate - Charles S. Robb (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - House of Representatives - General (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - House of Representatives - Virginia Congressmen (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Department of Agriculture (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Air Force (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Army (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Department of Army Corps of Engineers (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Department of Commerce (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Department of Defense (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Department of Education (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Department of Energy (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Department of Health and Human Services (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Department of Immigration and Naturalization (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Department of Interior (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Department of Justice (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Department of Labor (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Navy (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Department of State (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Department of Transportation (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Department of Transportation - Coast Guard (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Department of Transportation - Essential Air Service (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - Education Summit (part one) (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - Education Summit (part two) (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Education Summit (part three) (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Education Summit (part four) (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - General (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - General Services Administration (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - NASA (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - National Transportation Safety Board (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Attorney General (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Office of Technology Assessment (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Postal Service (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Small Business Administration (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Social Security Administration (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Supreme Court - Flag Decision (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Savings Bonds (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - White House (Box 190, Folder 11)
- Series V: 1990 (accession 33707)
  This series is organized into four sub-series: Governor's Office, Cabinet, General Assembly and United States Government and contains constituent correspondence from January 1-January 12, 1990.
  - Sub-Series A: Governor's Office
    - Constituent Correspondence (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Governor's General Correspondence (part one) (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Governor's General Correspondence (part two) (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1990 January (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series B: Cabinet
    - Secretary of Administration (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Secretary of Economic Development (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Secretary of Education (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Secretary of Finance (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series C: General Assembly
    - Correspondence (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series D: United States Government
    - Correspondence (Box 192, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous (accession 33707)
  This series includes materials from the Secretary of Human Resources, 1987, that was not included in the original transfer and records of Baliles tenure as chairman of the National Governors' Association from 1988 and 1989.
  - Sub-Series A: Secretary of Human Resources, 1987
    - Notes on provenance found on folders (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Deputy Secretary of Human Resources - Memos and Correspondence (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Aid to Dependent Children (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Certificate of Need (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Child Abuse (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Council on the Status of Women (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Department for the Aging (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Department for Children (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Department for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Department of Health (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series B: National Governors' Association, 1987-1989
    - Agriculture (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Budget/Federal (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Justice (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Economic Development/Technical Innovation (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Education Summit (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Energy and Environment (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Federalism (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - General (part one) (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - General (part two) (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - General (part three) (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - International Trade/Foreign Relations (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, 1989 (part one) (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Meetings, 1989 (part two) (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - 1990 Summer Meeting (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - 1991 Summer Meeting (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series C: Publications
    - America's Schools: Everybody's Business (U.S. Dept. of Education), nd (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - The Future of Agriculture, Forestry, Food Industries and Rural Communities in Virginia, Supplemental Report (Virginia Tech), January 1987 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Condition of the Commonwealth of Virginia, May 1983 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Record, 6-7 October 1989 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - The Enchanted Castle at Germanna, (Historic Gordonsville, Inc.), 1986 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - The Future of the Capital Area, 2000/2010: What it May Be-What It Should Be (VCU), ca. 1986 (2 volumes) (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - SCRRRAP: Governor's Paperwork Reduction Initiative (Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government), 1987 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Excellence in Education: A Plan for Virginia's Future (Report of the Governor's Commission on Excellence in Education), October 1986 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Toward a New Dominion: Choices for Virginians (Report of the Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future), December 1984 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Conference Proceedings (Governor's Conference on Critical Reevaluation), 23-24 September 1983 and An Assessment of the Secretarial System and Proposed Realignments of the Executive Branch, January 1984 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Historic St. Luke's, nd (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Department of Information Technology, February 1987 (2 volumes) (Box 196, Folder 12)